

CONTACT

- **** (803) 577-9188
- ✓ nicholasknight1999@gmail.com
- Columbia, SC
- https://nickkick909.github.io

EDUCATION

2017-2020 UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH CAROLINA

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science
- Magna Cum Laude

SKILLS

- Frontend Frameworks:
 - React
 - AngularJS
 - NextJS
 - VueJS
- Languages:
 - JavaScript
 - HTML
 - CSS
 - 。 C#
 - Python
- Database:
 - MySQL
 - Postgres
- Unity
- Docker
- AWS
- REST API

NICHOLAS KNIGHT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Highly motived software engineer with 4 years of full stack software development experience. Excited by learning and growing from being a part of new and challenging projects. Experienced with developing projects from the ground up, touching all parts of the project. Seeking to break into the professional game development industry using my years of software engineering knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Integer Technologies

MARCH 2023 - PRESENT

Software Engineer

- Develop user-facing HMI for Naval Power and Energy Systems project using AngularJS.
- Create a NodeJS REST API and WebSocket server for live data transfer to the HMI.
- Create an interactable 3D electrical system diagram using Unity and embedded it on the HMI.

Krumware LLC

May 2020 - March 2023

Software Engineer

- Create custom web applications, tailored to client's needs, deployed with AWS and Kubernetes/Docker infrastructure.
- Develop frontend UI using React, VueJS, and NextJS frameworks paired with JavaScript and GoLang REST API backends.

PROJECTS (GAME DEVELOPMENT)

Otter Adventures

JANUARY 2024 - PRESENT

- Work in progress.
- Pokémon styled game with an otter as the main character. Fight against other river animals. Level up to increase stats and learn new attacks.

GeoNova Gaming

February 2023 - August 2023

- Collaborate with a small team to develop a hyper casual mobile game.
- Integrate ads and resolve build issues for Android.

Dodge Car

December 2018

- Create simple game with a car moving forward on a platform dodging objects.
- First Unity experience, created over Winter break during sophomore vear.